Have you ever had a stressful day?
你曾经有过压力巨大的一天吗？
Many people do in the course of their daily lives.
很多人在日常生活中都会遇到这样的情况。
And on these high-pressure days, they might find themselves reaching for a sugary snack.
在这些高压的日子里，他们可能会发现自己伸手去拿含糖的零食。
Perhaps this is part of their daily routine.
也许这是他们日常生活的一部分。
Or perhaps on this particular day, their self-control is a bit low and they feel compelled to take a sugar hit.
又或许在这特别的一天，他们的自控力有点低，觉得不得不（compelled）吃点甜食。
Stress is natural.
有压力很正常。
That feeling of strain or pressure is a biological response, and under the right circumstances can be a great source of motivation.
那种紧张或压力的感觉是一种生理反应，在适当的情况下，它可以成为巨大的动力来源。
However, too much stress, especially chronic stress, has been linked to sleep disruption, a higher likelihood of a stroke, heart-attack, ulcer or depression, among other things.
然而，过多的压力，尤其是慢性的（chronic）压力，与许多疾病有关，比如睡眠紊乱、中风、心脏病、溃疡（ulcer）或抑郁等。
But why should stress make a person comfort eat?
但为什么压力会让人通过吃东西来寻求安慰呢？
Dr Giles Yeo, a member of the BBC’s Trust Me, I’m a Doctor team, got together with scientists from Leeds University to conduct an experiment into the effect of stress on blood sugar.
英国广播公司（BBC）《相信我，我是医生》节目组的成员贾尔斯・杨（Giles Yeo）博士与利兹大学（Leeds University）的科学家们一起进行了一项关于压力对血糖影响的实验。
Dr Yeo was subjected to a stress test.
杨博士接受了（subjected to）一项压力测试。
In the first stage, he was forced to answer mathematical questions rapidly.
在第一阶段，他被迫快速回答数学问题。
In the second, he had to immerse his hand in a bath of ice-cold water for a period of time.
在第二阶段，他不得不将手浸入（immerse）一盆冰冷的水中一段时间。
Before and after these tests, the Leeds scientists would measure Dr Yeo’s blood sugar levels.
在这些测试前后，利兹大学的科学家们会测量杨博士的血糖水平。
These are the levels which rise when we eat as our body takes in the energy of the food.
当我们进食时，随着身体吸收食物的能量，血糖水平会上升。
In a healthy person, these levels quickly return to normal.
在健康的人身上，这些水平会迅速恢复正常。
However, when Dr Yeo was being deliberately subjected to stress, his blood sugar took six times longer to drop than on a stress-free day.
然而，当杨博士故意处于压力之下时，他的血糖下降所需的时间是没有压力时的六倍。
When we become stressed, our bodies enter ‘fight or flight’ mode.
当我们感到压力时，我们的身体会进入“战斗或逃跑”模式。
Because our body believes it’s under attack, it releases glucose into the blood to provide energy for muscles.
因为我们的身体认为它受到了攻击，所以会释放葡萄糖（glucose）到血液中，为肌肉提供能量。
However, if we don’t use that energy, our body then releases insulin to make the blood sugar levels drop.
然而，如果我们不消耗这些能量，我们的身体就会释放胰岛素（insulin）来降低血糖水平。
This drop causes a hunger response: you want to eat.
这种下降会引发饥饿反应：你想吃东西。
And what you particularly crave is sugary food, which rapidly replenishes the energy you have lost.
而你特别渴望（crave）的是含糖食物，它能迅速补充你失去的能量。
If this happens repeatedly, over a long enough period of time, these high-calorie foods can lead to obesity.
如果这种情况反复发生，在足够长的一段时间内，这些高热量食物会导致肥胖。
So what can we do to combat the stress?
那么我们能做些什么来对抗压力呢？
In an article for the BBC, Dr Michael Mosley recommends ‘stress-busting’ techniques, like exercise, gardening, mindfulness or another activities that you enjoy.
迈克尔・莫斯利（Michael Mosley）博士在为BBC撰写的一篇文章中推荐了“减压”技巧，比如锻炼、园艺、正念冥想（mindfulness）或其他你喜欢的活动。
But his strongest recommendation is trying to get a good night’s sleep.
但他最强烈的建议是尽量睡个好觉。
A recent study carried out by researchers at King's College, London found that if you deprived people of sleep, they would consume, on average, an extra 385kcal per day, which is equivalent to the calories in a large muffin.
伦敦国王学院（King's College, London）的研究人员最近进行的一项研究发现，如果你剥夺（deprived）人们的睡眠，他们平均每天会多摄入385千卡的热量，这相当于一个大松饼的热量。
So, try sleeping to decrease stress, and as a result make it easier to keep yourself a little trimmer.
所以，尝试通过睡眠来减轻压力，也能因此更容易让自己保持苗条一点（trimmer）。